<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ToDo Task</string>
    <string name="title_activity_navigation">NavigationActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bottom_navigation">BottomNavigationActivity</string>
    <string name="title_calendar">Календарь</string>
    <string name="title_board">Доска задач</string>
    <string name="title_chat">Чат</string>
    <string name="title_daily_log">Ежедневник</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_active_desk">ActiveDesk</string>
    <string name="title_activity_setting_">Setting_Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main__setting_">Main_Setting_Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_app_scrolling_activity">About_app_scrolling_activity</string>
    <string name="developers_text">
        " ИКБО-03-17\n"
        "Башкин Антон\n"
        "Большаков Сергей\n"
        "Карчевский Дмитрий\n"
        "Судариков Кирилл\n"
        "Чекановкин Андрей\n"
        "Шачнов Никита\n"
        "Шведков Иван\n"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Данный органайзер содержит все необходимые элементы, которые могут пригодиться в "
        "повседневной жизни человека. Так же данное приложение удобно использовать для командной"
        "работы над чем-либо или же просто общения.\n"
        "Так, данное приложение содержит:"
        "Заметки, разделённые на несколько категорий (ежедневник, планирование, и заметки).\n"
        "Календарь с отображением ваших планов по датам.\n"
        "Доска задач с доступом для команды. Чтобы можно было легко ставить задачи на команду и их"
        "распределять.\n"
        "Чат.\n"
        "\n Это краткое описание, которое нужно дополнить. Далее текст для примера: \n\n"
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_chat_add">Chat_add</string>
</resources>
